Hello everyone, this is Masuda Konoka.
I've come up with some easy full-body stretches for you this time.
Let's work hard together.
Okay, first of all, sit cross-legged.
We'll start with neck stretches.
First of all, we're going to start with a right-handed turn2 and then we're going to start with a neck stretch. First, right turn.
Two turns each.
Left.
Check to see if there's anything that sticks out, and do it as far as you can move it.
Then, roll forward.
Do not press too hard.
Stretch it out as if you are leaving the weight of your head on it.
Go backward.
Next, go to the right.
Left.
Then rotate your shoulders.
Move your back and shoulder blades from the front.
If you have room, you can do it with your elbows on the floor.
Turn the opposite way, from the back.
Next, do the arms.
You may get tired easily from using the phone or something.
Do the other side too.
You may forget to stretch your arms, but they are also important.
Next, stretch your armpits.
Let's try the left arm, and see if it stretches.
Opposite side
Reverse side
Now stretch the armpit.
If you feel you can go a little bit further.
You can also turn your body down on your side.
Then bend forward with the right leg in front of you.
If you are still able to do it
If you are still able to do it, move both halves of your body to the left side to make it easier to stretch.
Even if you don't put your hips and lower back on the floor so firmly, you can stretch your hips and lower back.
If you feel that your hips and lower back are stretched, it's okay.
Next, bend forward again with your left leg in front of you.
If you want to stretch it more, move it to the right side.
Breathe well.
All right.
Now we're going to stretch the soles of your feet.
Now, we're going to do about a 90-degree angle here.
Start with your right foot.
Work as hard as you can until you can touch your feet as much as possible.
If you have room, just flop down.
If you point your toes to the ceiling, you can get more stretch.
I always check my nails here.
Nails are in good shape.
Then go to the side.
If you still have room, try stretching at a wider angle than here.
Stretch from the waist to the stomach and down the side of the body.
Now let's do the left side again.
Stretch the back side.
Check the first one.
I'm saying something again.
It's not necessary to check the nails.
Okay, and now we're going to stretch this side, this side of the body.
If there's room, we'll widen the angle.
This is where we're going to stretch it out.
And breathe.
Okay.
And now we're going to stretch your front thighs.
Now we're going to start with your right leg down.
And then we're going to stretch the front of your leg so that it's at a 90-degree angle here.
You want to make sure that your knee doesn't extend past your heel.
Now we're going to extend your front thigh.
Then go deep down.
If you feel a stretch in your hips here, you're good to go.
Lastly, bend this leg.
Hold your toes.
Bring it back as far as you can.
Try it.
If you can do it, try to do it so well that you can feel your heel against your buttocks.
Now let's move on to the left leg.
Keep going in the opposite direction.
Bend your leg 90 degrees here.
Now go deeper.
Put your elbows on the floor.
Then you'll feel more of a stretch in your hip area.
Then you're going to get more hip flexion.
Then bend your knees again and catch your toes.
Now you're almost there... and your front thighs will feel better, so I recommend you do this.
All right.
All right, that's it.
I hope you were able to stretch it out.
You can do this stretch in the morning when you wake up and want to feel refreshed.
It's also perfect to do it at night after taking a bath.
or before or after muscle training.
or when you want to feel refreshed.
Anyway, you can do this stretch anywhere and anytime.
I hope you will make it a habit to do this stretch.
Let's work together with me!
So, thank you very much.
Please come back to do it again.